malwarehelp.org 2012-03-08

# Privacy Policy — Malware Help. Org

**Malware Help. Org** values our relationship with you and the other visitors of our Web site. We recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in mind.

We have implemented this Privacy Policy to inform you of the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it.

 **What types of information does Malware Help. Org collect from me?**

Malware Help. Org collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This log information cannot be easily used to personally identify you. It includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, the date and time of each access request, the URL of the previous Web site you visited, operating system, and your IP Address.

 **How and when does Malware Help. Org collect this information?**

Like the operators of most Web sites, we use analytic and reporting technologies to record non-personal information such as Internet domain and host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser software and operating system types.

 **How does Malware Help. Org use my information?**

We use this information to operate, develop, evaluate, and improve our services.

 **What about cookies?**

 **Malware Help. Org** does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on **Malware Help. Org**.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to **Malware Help. Org** and other sites on the Internet. 

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….Google Adsense, Commission Junction, Linkshare among others. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on **Malware Help. Org** send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

**Malware Help. Org** has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.malwarehelp.org’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Does this privacy policy apply when I access third party Web sites?**

You may be able to access third-party Web sites directly from our Web Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply when you access such Web sites. We cannot control how third parties may use Personal Information you disclose to them, so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third-party web site you visit before using it or disclosing your Personal Information to its provider.

 **More**

Whatever information/comments submitted using the webforms are going to be read only by me unless I choose to publish them elsewhere on this Website.

If you choose to email me and provide personally identifiable information about yourself, I will not use the information for any purpose other than to respond to your inquiry.

If you have any questions or comments, you are welcome to contact me using the [Contact Form](http://www.malwarehelp.org/contact.html).

 **Malware Help. Org** reserves the right to make modifications to these policies at any time without prior notification and at our discretion. Such modifications will be posted here as they become effective.
